Protection is out of the question
Contracted: Phase II is a horror, thriller film directed by Josh Forbes.
Picking up directly where the previous film left off, the story follows Riley, one of the last people to come in contact with Samantha, as he scrambles to
track down those responsible for the outbreak before the highly contagious disease not only consumes his body, but the world as we know it.
Riley, played by Matt Mercer.
Crystal Young, played by Marianna Palka.
BJ, played by Morgan Peter Brown.
Harper, played by Anna Lore.
Brenda, played by Laurel Vail.
Samantha, played by Najarra Townsend.
Contracted: Phase II is a 2015 American zombie-body horror
independent film and the sequel to the 2013 film Contracted.
The film was directed by Josh Forbes, based on a
script written by Craig Walendziak.
Phase II features most of the actors and actresses from the original cast of the first film, and follows Riley (Matt Mercer)
as he tries to find the man behind the sexually transmitted disease causing a viral outbreak in Los Angeles.
The film had its world premiere on July 5, 2015, at the
Neuchâtel International Fantastic Film Festival.
The film explores themes of infection, sequel, virus.
The tone is dark and intense.